(Mrs Cooper:)I know how to take care of my baby.
(Mrs Cooper:)His eyes came out a little thin,
but you can just pretend he's Chinese.
(Mrs Cooper:)So do you want to talk
about what happened...
(Mrs Cooper:)...with you and your little friends?
(Sheldon:)-They're not my friends.
-All right.
[MARY CHUCKLES]
(Mrs Cooper:)If you recall, when you were little
we sat right here at this very spot...
...and talked about the problems you had
getting along with the neighbor kids.
(Sheldon:)That was different. They were
threatened by my intelligence...
(Sheldon:)...and too stupid to know
that's why they hated me.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, baby, they knew very well
why they hated you.
(Howard:)I can't believe
you bought a red cowboy hat.
(Howard:)Hello? I'm wearing a red turtleneck.